import 'package:quiz_app_tutorial/models/question.dart';

const List<Question> mathQuestions = [
  Question(
    question: '1. What is the result of 5 x 8?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 25',
      'b) 40',
      'c) 56',
      'd) 64',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '2. Solve: 12 ÷ 3?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) 4',
      'b) 6',
      'c) 9',
      'd) 12',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '3. Calculate: 7² - 3²',
    correctAnswerIndex: 3,
    options: [
      'a) 16',
      'b) 20',
      'c) 24',
      'd) 40',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '4. What is the square root of 144?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 8',
      'b) 12',
      'c) 16',
      'd) 20',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '5. If x = 3, what is the value of 2x + 5?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 8',
      'b) 11',
      'c) 13',
      'd) 16',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '6. What is the result of 9² ÷ 3?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 21',
      'b) 27',
      'c) 36',
      'd) 45',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '7. If y = 2 and z = 5, what is y + z?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    options: [
      'a) 5',
      'b) 7',
      'c) 8',
      'd) 10',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '8. Solve: 15 - 6 x 2 + 4',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) 7',
      'b) 11',
      'c) 7',
      'd) 19',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '9. What is the product of 9 and 7?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    options: [
      'a) 63',
      'b) 72',
      'c) 81',
      'd) 90',
    ],
  ),
  Question(
    question: '10. If a rectangle has a length of 8 units and a width of 5 units, what is its area?',
    correctAnswerIndex: 2,
    options: [
      'a) 13 square units',
      'b) 30 square units',
      'c) 40 square units',
      'd) 48 square units',
    ],
  ),
];
